大家好
我是小武
今天和大家一同观赏的是
2019年全英公开赛男单决赛
由日本选手桃田贤斗对阵丹麦选手安赛龙
Say that to be arson and big tg
Having the same
Playing style
They look the same
And so on
But it's actually not true in the sense that
抛下压
anna entence is龙连续空
When it comes to his follow up
Yeah
and that's so抓推
When you play someone like
空转身抛抓推突击得分
Now it's playing on this is
This is the favorite shot from the motor
The smash down
五比二龙控正手逃过渡后场
触发了龙的丹麦传统艺能
Hey
Watch this
Watch
This is gonna leave it and leave it
Oh gonna play it
Ha hall england
Final isn't the moment for exhibition
Trick shots
六比二龙连续控正手
抓推
往前分对角平高逼
摆脱杀上网连贯得分
The big and then follow up
七比三曹抓推龙接杀
转对角抓推突击得手
And from the situation two good defensive shots
This one cross court
Then the lift
And then that counter attacking
七比四龙头顶突击
直线调控
正手龙同样控正手
再控正手朝斜线过渡
龙放网踢掉斜线
控正手抓过度劈杀斜线
逃挡网化解龙挑球很到位
机会不好逃
选择过度停顿
推转身滑板掉一拍停顿推转身挡原网
踢掉斜线得手
九比四
好抓推放网下压
逃房返
放网轮回沟
高质量平高
使淘判断失误
太费无比
九龙花后场空头顶抓摆脱
侧身杀一拍淘接杀转对角龙控头顶抓过度
侧身杀直线得分
第六比九龙发后场分对角
使桃被动往前扑杀得手
七比九好假动作
分球严控头顶投篮掉
化解抢原网抓推
The polls
桃勾对角逼起球
下压龙顶
后场破坏连贯
龙连续控两底线
豪华版斜线
豪连续控两底线
龙过渡后场控网操控正手
下压空转身龙反拍过渡
后场高质量平高
使陶判断失误
And mamotors is waiting for the attacking shots
The downwards shot
and then this10比八好抓we龙
高质量挡网化解操控转身龙抽直线摆脱操控
正手往前分对角龙同样控正手接杀挡斜线
摆脱龙控头顶陶软压宝
主动往前分对角
双方斗网
龙挑球很到位
机会不好逃
选择过度龙挡远网
抓推突击得分
Well
Opening again
I was scared that the match might develop
So much better for we
曹
同样抓推高点蓝调迫使龙挑球出界
Let's go long to the mid game interval mark
11比九龙空头顶光摆脱
Take a little bit more chances at the front
龙推转身逃过度
后场龙底线判断犹豫逃抓摆脱头顶杀直线得分
From texas was all in bang
12比九龙控正手逃出斜线摆脱逃抓推
龙控正手放网
侧身杀一拍
推球逼过度起跳
重杀得分
Ten twelve
十比12龙发
后场控正手头劈掉一拍
家里抽直线
龙控头顶豪华版掉一拍
重杀追身得分
Good smash was difficult for the tall players
13比十龙控头顶桃软压宝
主动远网转近网
龙回搓抓推好党网
化解双方斗网
陶平高拉开龙下
压好党网
摆脱
龙钓鱼头顶杀直线操控
正手放远网抓推
龙接杀转对角被动但被击杀
斜线得分
And in kong
Yesterday
Did that really well
15比11龙甲动作分球抛回缩杀
追身龙控正手挡远网
抓推陶泄力
挡网
化解连续控两底线
It's interesting that is not really using his very net
Play
网前对角变化
Is lifting most socing most away from the net
斜线过渡逃回搓高质量高呼得分
It is
But this is one of the first few times
He's actually done this
And he's got an excellent
16比11龙控正手逃出直线
摆脱龙
反抽斜线停顿推转身发过度进攻好倒地救球
龙推球逼过度
但中扎下网
17比11
郝景丁推球拦截龙控网抢攻
回搓要求质量太高
导致下网20比11龙控网好
挑球很到位
龙强行下压好
高质量挡网得手
拿下了首局的胜利
And twenty one eleven
第二局零比零横空
头顶300多进攻
But then half smashes
First toten for the big ones after that
but龙推球拉开
豪佳丽抽直线放网
龙回勾
This is will be trying to further
Think you will get trouble
Yeah
One h
一比一调控正手分球抢攻
停顿放网
踢掉斜线
龙网前勾对角抓推控网操控正手抓过度进攻
高质量回搓抓扑得分
No he casually moving around in the court
And say arti
Hot poleon ww over
And here it comes going for a big one
Then it's coming back
But look at this one
Then the second one is coming as well
You are not
比泽三比一龙空网抢攻得分
二比三龙发后场韩后场比摆脱头顶重杀得分
Trying to stress mamotvt o
And that was much more about angle
Rather than power
三平
隆平高控正手网前分对角再度平高控正手
好软鸭龙网前转对角
加力抽直线
逃控转身龙底线判断犹豫
陶平高拉开
龙抓过度进攻
陶鱼跃救球
龙网前停顿
平高拉开
好软压龙控
正手抓过度
侧身杀大斜线得分
He had to do it for three
So how is falling out of court
四比三
龙控头顶好往前转
对角侧身杀一拍
龙控头顶抓过度
头顶杀斜线得分
Five three
四比五龙控正手抛出直线摆脱
龙推球逼过度
头顶杀一拍
龙回搓高质量good飞起跳
重杀直线
豪杰杀挡直线弹网得分
First a very very good lift
But deflected on the next
六比五
龙控网抢攻得分
Can do
六平调控
转身挡
远网抓推突击得分
Oh seven six
七比六好抓推one day
再度抓推糕点
放网下压龙控头
顶好软鸭
双方斗网
龙岗原网抓推
推球逼转身
抓过度
头顶拦截得分
七平豪接发假动作
阮鸭宝主动龙井丁推球拦截
往前扑杀得分
There's the follow up you
Hanna anson
Son was very successful doing
When he played mamotor in the indonesian
八平双方斗网
龙侧身杀一拍
往前勾
对角被抓
That's one of the u shots that axis
And is playing quite a lot
And he's following routine
九比8nets
龙科瓦抢攻得手
To predic
九平龙抓推
空头顶好软鸭龙在空头顶抓
摆脱进攻
连贯得分
Ten nine
Yeah
Good play there
十比九豪控正手分球抢攻得手
十平龙控头顶抓摆
脱掉一拍
豪分球抢攻得分
Oh that is absolutely
Super
Finding the line
龙接下来会怎样调整呢
豪会顺利拿下全英冠军吗
预知后续如何
我们下期一同观赏
我只